Get back, get back, get back, get back, get back.
The city's rebelling against the federal government.
Just like in Chicago, Portland PD won't keep federal agents safe either.
They actually slapped them with a zoning violation for boarding up their building's windows
so Antifa can't see inside.
They believe women have a right to privacy, just not ICE.
An ICE facility was just shot up in Dallas.
And now cartels have put bounties on their heads.
They're making plans to ambush them and to kill them.
We have specific officers and agents that have bounties that have been put out on their
heads.
It's been $2,000 to kidnap them, $10,000 to kill them.
We're trying to protect the country from cartels and they're saying we're at war with Americans
and Kristi Noem should be charged with war crimes.